<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<component type="desktop">
  <id>xfce4-power-manager.desktop</id>
  <metadata_license>CC-BY-3.0</metadata_license>
  <project_license>GPL-2.0+</project_license>
  <name>Xfce power manager</name>
  <summary>Manage and reduce power consumption of computer and devices</summary>

  <description>
    <p>Xfce power manager manages the power sources on the computer and the devices that can be controlled to reduce their power consumption (such as LCD brightness level, monitor sleep, CPU frequency scaling).</p>
    <p xml:lang="bg">Xfce power manager управлява източници на захранване на компютъра и устройствата, които могат да бъдат контролирани, за да се намали потреблението на енергия (като ниво на яркост на LCD, монитор, сън, честотата на процесора).</p>
    <p xml:lang="cs">Správa napájení pro Xfce spravuje zdroje napájení počítače a zařízení, která lze ovládat za účelem snížení spotřeby energie (např. úroveň jasu LCD displeje, uspání monitoru, nastavení frekvence procesoru).</p>
    <p xml:lang="da">Xfce-strømstyringen håndterer strømkilderne på computeren og de enheder, der kan justeres til at spare på strømmen (såsom lysstyrken på LCD-skærmen, sluk for skærm og skalering af CPU-frekvens).</p>
    <p xml:lang="de">Die Xfce-Energieverwaltung verwaltet die Energiequellen des Rechners und die Geräte, die gesteuert werden können, um ihren Energieverbrauch zu reduzieren (wie zum Beispiel LCD-Helligkeit, Stromsparmodus des Bildschirms, CPU-Frequenzskalierung).</p>
    <p xml:lang="en_AU">Xfce power manager manages the power sources on the computer and the devices that can be controlled to reduce their power consumption (such as LCD brightness level, monitor sleep, CPU frequency scaling).</p>
    <p xml:lang="es">El Administrador de energía de Xfce gestiona las fuentes de alimentación del equipo y de los dispositivos que puedan controlarse para reducir su consumo de energía (por ejemplo, nivel de brillo del LCD, apagar el monitor, escalado de frecuencia del procesador).</p>
    <p xml:lang="fi">Xfce:n virranhallinta hallitsee tietokoneen virtalähteitä ja laitteita, joiden virrankäyttöä voidaan vähentää (esimerkiksi näytön kirkkauden taso ja lepotila, prosessorin tehon säätö).</p>
    <p xml:lang="fr">Le gestionnaire d’alimentation Xfce gère les sources d’alimentation sur l’ordinateur et les périphériques qui peuvent être contrôlés afin de réduire leur consommation d’énergie (tel que le niveau de luminosité de l’écran LCD, la mise en veille du moniteur, l’échelonnement de la fréquence du CPU). </p>
    <p xml:lang="he">מנהל צריכת חשמל Xfce מנהל את מקורות החשמל של המחשב וההתקנים שניתן לשלוט בהם כדי להפחית את צריכת החשמל שלהם (כגון רמת בהירות המסך, כיבוי התצוגה, שינוי תדירות פעולות המעבד).</p>
    <p xml:lang="hr">Xfce upravitelj energijom upravlja izvorima energije računala i uređajima kojima se može smanjiti razina potrošnje energije (kao što su razina svjetline LCD zaslona, spavanje monitora, promijena frekvencije CPU-a).</p>
    <p xml:lang="it">Il gestore di energia di Xfce controlla le fonti di energia del computer e dei dispositivi che possono essere controllati per ridurre il loro consumo (come luminosità dello schermo, spegnimento del monitor o frequenza della CPU).</p>
    <p xml:lang="ja">Xfce 電源管理はコンピューターおよび消費電力を制御可能なデバイス (LCD の輝度レベル、モニターのスリープ、CPU の動作周波数など) の電源を管理します。</p>
    <p xml:lang="kk">Xfce эл. қорегін басқарушысы компьютердің эл. қорек көздерін және қоректі тұтынуды баптауға болатын құрылғыларды (LCD экран жарықтылығы, мониторды ұйықтату, процессор жиілігін өзгерту сияқты) басқарады.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ko">Xfce 전원 관리자는 컴퓨터와 전력 소모 감소를 제어(LCD 밝기, 모니터 대기 상태, CPU 주파수 조정)할 수 있는 장치에 붙은 전원을 관리합니다.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ms">Pengurus kuasa Xfce mengurus sumber kuasa pada komputer dan peranti yang dapat dikawal untuk mengurangkan penggunaan kuasa mereka (seperti aras kecerahan LCD, mod tidur monitor, penskalaan frekuensi CPU).</p>
    <p xml:lang="nb">Xfce effektbehanlder tar hånd om effektkildene på maskinen og enhetene som kan kontrolleres for å redusere deres effektforbruk (som lysnivå på LCD-skjerm, søvn for monitor, og skalering av prosessor).</p>
    <p xml:lang="nl">Xfce Energiebeheerder beheert de krachtbronnen op de computer en de apparaten waarvan het stroomverbruik kan worden teruggebracht (zoals schermhelderheid, slaapstand van beeldscherm, verlagen van CPU-frequentie).</p>
    <p xml:lang="pl">Menedżer zasilania Xfce odpowiada za zarządzanie poborem energii przez komputer oraz urządzenia do niego podłączone (np. dopasowując jasność ekranu, wstrzymując działanie monitora, przeskalowując taktowanie CPU).</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt">O gestor de energia Xfce faz a gestão das fontes de energia no computador e em dispositivos que possam ser controlados para reduzir seu consumo de energia ( Tal como nivel de luminosidade do LCD, Suspensão do monitor, escalonamento da frequência do CPU).</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt_BR">O gerenciador de energia do Xfce gerencia as fontes de energia no computador e os dispositivos que podem ser controlados para reduzir o seu consumo de energia (como o nível de brilho do LCD, monitorar suspensão, escalonamento da frequência do CPU).</p>
    <p xml:lang="ro">Managerul de consum Xfce gestionează sursele de curent ale sistemului și dispozitivele ce pot fi controlate pentru a reduce consumul de curent, de exemplu prin reducerea luminozității ecranelor LCD, ori trecerea lor în repaus, scalarea frecvenței procesoarelor etc.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ru">Менеджер питания Xfce управляет источниками питания компьютера и устройств, которые имеют такую возможность, для снижения энергопотребления (например, яркость подсветки экрана, ждущий решим монитора, изменение частоты процессора).</p>
    <p xml:lang="sk">Správca napájania Xfce  spravuje zdroje napájania počítača a zariadenia, ktorým možno riadiť potrebu napájania (napr. úroveň jasu LCD, uspanie monitora, nastavenie frekvencie CPU).</p>
    <p xml:lang="sl">Upravljalnik porabe energije Xfce upravlja z viri energije na računalniku in napravami, ki jih lahko nadzoruje za zmanjšanje porabe energije (knp. svetlost LCD zaslonov, mirovanje zaslonov, nadzorovanje hitrosti procesorja).</p>
    <p xml:lang="sr">Управник потрошње Иксфце-а управља потрошачима на рачунару и уређајима којима може да се управља ради штедње (као што су ступањ осветљења ЛЦД-а, успављивање екрана, подешавање учесталости процесора).</p>
    <p xml:lang="th">ระบบจัดการพลังงานของ Xfce จะจัดการแหล่งพลังงานของคอมพิวเตอร์และอุปกรณ์ต่างๆ ที่สามารถควบคุมได้ เพื่อลดการใช้พลังงานของอุปกรณ์เหล่านั้น (เช่น ระดับความสว่างของ LCD, การหลับของจอภาพ, การปรับความถี่ซีพียู)</p>
    <p xml:lang="tr">Xfce güç yöneticisi bilgisayarda ve kendi güç tüketimini azaltmak için(LCD parlaklık seviyesi, monitör uyku modu, MİB frekans ölçekleme gibi)  kontrol edilebilir cihazlarda  güç kaynaklarını yönetir. </p>
    <p xml:lang="uk">Менеджер живлення Xfce керує джерелами живлення комп’ютера і пристроями, які можна контролювати, зменшуючи споживання енергії ними (такі, як рівень яскравості LCD, монітор сплячки, шкалювання частотою процесора).</p>
    <p xml:lang="zh_CN">Xfce 电源管理器管理计算机的电源以及能够控制并降低功耗的设备（例如液晶显示器亮度级别，显示器睡眠，CPU频率等等）。</p>
    <p xml:lang="zh_TW">Xfce 電源管理員管理在您的電腦及裝置上的電力來源，可以減少電力消耗(像是液晶螢幕的亮度、顯示器睡眠、CPU時脈調整等)。</p>
    <p>In addition, Xfce power manager provides a set of freedesktop-compliant DBus interfaces to inform other applications about current power level so that they can adjust their power consumption, and it provides the inhibit interface which allows applications to prevent automatic sleep actions via the power manager; as an example, the operating system’s package manager should make use of this interface while it is performing update operations.</p>
    <p xml:lang="bg">В допълнение, Xfce Power Manager предоставя набор от freedesktop-съвместими DBUS интерфейси за информиране за текущото ниво на мощност на други приложения, така че те да могат да коригират тяхното потребление на енергия, и осигурява интерфейс който позволява на приложенията да предотвратяват автоматичното заспиване чрез управлението на захранването; като пример, за управление на мениджъра на пакети докато се извършва актуализация.</p>
    <p xml:lang="cs">Dále Správce napájení pro Xfce poskytuje sadu rozhraní sběrnice DBus v souladu s prvky freedesktop tak, že informuje ostatní aplikace o současné úrovni napájení, aby mohly přizpůsobit svoji spotřebu energie, a poskytuje aplikacím rozhraní pro předejití automatizovaných akcí pro přechod do režimu spánku. Toto rozhraní využívá například Správce balíčků systému při instalaci aktualizací.</p>
    <p xml:lang="da">I tillæg tilbyder Xfce-strømstyringen et sæt af freedesktop-kompatible DBus-grænseflader, der informerer andre programmer om det aktuel strømstyrkeniveau, så de kan tilpasse deres strømforbrug, samtidig som det tilbyder inhibit-grænsefladen, der gør det muligt for programmer, at forhindre automatiske hvilehandlinger via strømhåndteringen; som eksempel bør operativsystemets pakkehåndtering gøre brug denne grænseflade, mens den udfører opdateringshandlinger.</p>
    <p xml:lang="de">Zusätzlich stellt die Xfce-Energieverwaltung einen Satz an Freedesktop-konformen DBus-Schnittstellen zur Verfügung, um andere Anwendungen über den aktuellen Energiestand zu informieren, sodass diese ihren Energieverbrauch anpassen bzw. das automatische Versetzen in den Bereitschaftsmodus oder Ruhezustand verhindern können; beispielsweise sollte die Paketverwaltung des Betriebssystems diese Schnittstelle während der Aktualisierungsvorgänge benutzen.</p>
    <p xml:lang="en_AU">In addition, Xfce power manager provides a set of freedesktop-compliant DBus interfaces to inform other applications about current power level so that they can adjust their power consumption, and it provides the inhibit interface which allows applications to prevent automatic sleep actions via the power manager; as an example, the operating system’s package manager should make use of this interface while it is performing update operations.</p>
    <p xml:lang="es">Además, el Administrador de energía de Xfce proporciona un conjunto de interfaces «D-Bus» utilizando las especificaciones de «freedesktop» para informar a otras aplicaciones sobre el nivel de energía actual para que puedan ajustar su consumo, y proporciona una interfaz de inhibición que permite a las aplicaciones evitar acciones automáticas de suspensión a través del administrador de energía; como por ejemplo, el gestor de paquetes del sistema operativo debe hacer uso de esta interfaz mientras se está llevando a cabo operaciones de actualización.</p>
    <p xml:lang="fi">Lisäksi Xfce:n virranhallinta tarjoaa joitakin freedesktop-yhteensopivia DBus-rajapintoja ilmoittaakseen muille sovelluksille virran tasosta jotta ne voivat säätää omaa virrankulustaan ja jotta automaattinen keskeytys- ja lepotilaan siirtyminen voidaan välttää; esimerkiksi järjestelmän pakettienhallinnan tulisi käyttää tätä rajapintaa suorittaessaan päivitystoimintoja.</p>
    <p xml:lang="fr">De plus, le gestionnaire d’alimentation Xfce fournit un ensemble d’interfaces DBus conformes aux spécifications freedesktop pour informer les autres applications du niveau de charge actuel afin qu’elles puissent ajuster leur consommation d’énergie, et il fournit l’interface d’inhibition qui permet aux applications d’empêcher les actions automatiques de mise en veille via le gestionnaire d’alimentation ; par exemple, le gestionnaire de paquets du système d’exploitation devrait faire usage de cette interface pendant qu’il effectue ses opérations de mise à jour.</p>
    <p xml:lang="he">בנוסף, מנהל צריכת החשמל של Xfce מספק ערכה של מנשקי DBus תומכי freedesktop כדי ליידע יישומים אחרים על צריכת החשמל הנוכחית כדי שיוכלו להתאים את צריכת החשמל שלהם וכמו כן מספקת את מנשק המניעה שמאפשר ליישומים למנוע פעילות שינה אוטומטית באמצעות מנהל צריכת החשמל; לדוגמה, מנהל החבילות של מערכת ההפעלה צריך להשתמש במנשק זה בעת ביצוע פעולות עדכון.</p>
    <p xml:lang="hr">Uz to, Xfce upravitelj energijom pruža set DBus sučelja usklađenih s freedesktop standardom radi obaviještavanja drugih aplikacija o trenutnom stanju energije kako bi mogle prilagoditi svoju razinu potrošnje. Pruža i sučelje koje omogućava aplikacijama da zaustave automatsko spavanje sustava, npr. dok upravitelj programskim paketima ažurira sustav.</p>
    <p xml:lang="it">In più, il gestore di energia di Xfce fornisce una serie di interfacce DBus compatibili con freedesktop, allo scopo di informare le altre applicazioni riguardo il livello energetico del sistema così da permettere loro di regolarsi in base ad esso. Fornisce inoltre un'interfaccia che consente di selezionare quali applicazioni possono impedire l'addormentamento automatico del sistema attraverso il gestore di energia; ad esempio il gestore di pacchetti del sistema può utilizzare questa interfaccia mentre sta effettuando gli aggiornamenti.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ja">さらに、Xfce 電源管理はほかのアプリケーションに現在の電源レベルなどを提供するための freedesktop.org 準拠の DBus インターフェイスも用意しています。これを利用してアプリケーションから消費電力の調整が行えます。ほかに、電源制御が自動で行うスリープの一時的な抑止もできます。例えば、オペレーティングシステムのパッケージ管理がアップデート処理を行っている間などにこの機能を使用するといいでしょう。</p>
    <p xml:lang="kk">Сонымен қатар, Xfce эл. қорегін басқарушысы басқа қолданбаларға ағымдағы эл. қорек деңгейі туралы ақпаратты ұсынуға арналған freedesktop-үйлесімді DBus интерфейстерін қамтамасыз етеді. Оның көмегімен қолданбалар өздерінің қоректі тұтыну деңгейлерін баптап, ұйықтатуға жол бермеу мүмкіндігін пайдалана алады. Мысалы, жүйені жаңартатын дестелер басқарушысы өз жұмысын сәтті аяқтау үшін оны қолдана алады.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ko">게다가, Xfce 전원 관리자에서는 현재 전원 상태를 다른 프로그램에 제공하는 freedesktop 호환 DBus 인터페이스를 제공하여 전력 소모를 줄일 수 있고, 전원 관리자가 자동으로 대기상태로 진입하는 동작을 다른 프로그램이 막을 수 있게 하는 억제 인터페이스를 제공합니다. 예를 들자면 운영체제 꾸러미 관리자에서는 업데이트 동작을 수행하는 동안 이 인터페이스를 활용합니다.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ms">Tambahan pula, pengurus kuasa Xfce menyediakan satu set antaramuka DBus menuruti-freedesktop untuk memaklumkan aplikasi lain mengenai aras kuasa semasa supaya ia dapat melaras penggunaan kuasa mereka, dan ia menyediakan juga antaramuka rencat yang membolehkan aplikasi menghalang tindakan tidur automatik melalui pengurus kuasa; contohnya, pengurus pakej sistem pengoperasian menggunakan antaramuka ini ketika ia membuat kemaskini operasi.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nb">I tillegg vil har Xfce effektbehandler et knippe freedesktop-støttede DBus-grensesnitt for å informere programmer om gjeldende effektnivå så de kan regulere sitt effektforbruk, og det hindrer dvalgang, hvilket lar programmer hindre automatisk dvalemodus gjort av effektbehandleren; som et eksempel gjør pakkebehandleren bruk av dette grensesnittet når den utfører oppdateringer.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nl">Bovendien levert Xfce Energiebeheerder een stel DBus-bedieningsschillen die voldoen aan de freedesktop-standaard, om andere toepassingen in te lichten omtrent het huidige energieniveau, zodat zij hun energieverbruik kunnen bijstellen. Ook levert hij aan toepassingen de bedieningsschil om automatische slaapstand via Energiebeheerder te voorkomen. Bijvoorbeeld: de pakketbeheerder van het besturingssysteem zou deze bedieningsschil moeten gebruiken wanneer hij programma's aan het bijwerken is.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt">Em complemento, o gestor de energia Xfce proporciona um conjunto interfaces de ambientes de trabalho gratuitos DBus compativeis para informar outras aplicações sobre o atual nivel de energia para que possam ajustar seu nivel de consumo de energia e proporciona o interface de inibição que permite as aplicações que previnam as ações automaticas de suspensão através do gestor de energia; como exemplo, o gestor de pacotes do sistema operativo deverá utilizar este interface enquanto está realizando operações de atualização.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt_BR">Além disso, o gerenciador de energia do Xfce fornece um conjunto de interfaces DBus compatíveis com o freedesktop para informar outros aplicativos sobre o nível de energia atual, para que possam ajustar seu consumo de energia, e fornece a interface de inibição, que permite que os aplicativos evitem ações automáticas de suspensão através do gerenciador de energia; por exemplo, o gerenciador de pacotes do sistema operacional deve fazer uso dessa interface, enquanto ele estiver executando operações de atualização.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ro">În plus, managerul de consum Xfce oferă un set de interfețe DBus ce respectă standardele freedesktop.org pentru a informa alte programe despre nivelul bateriei, astfel încât acestea să-și ajusteze consumul de curent. Mai mult, oferă o interfață de prevenire a trecerii automate în repaus pentru programele ce necesită continuarea funcționării pentru o perioadă de timp, de exemplu un manager de pachete ce actualizează sistemul.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ru">Дополнительно, менеджер питания Xfce предоставляет набор интерфейсов DBus, совместимых с freedesktop, для оповещения других приложений о текущем уровне заряда, чтобы они могли изменить своё потребление энергии. Также имеется интерфейс, позволяющий приложениям запретить автоматические действия для ждущего режима в менеджере питания, например, менеджер пакетов операционной системы должен использовать данный интерфейс при выполнении операций по обновлению.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sk">Ďalej, Správca napájania Xfce poskytuje sadu rozhraní DBus zhodných s freedesktop na informovanie iných aplikácií o aktuálnej úrovni napájania, aby mohli prispôsobiť svoju spotrebu a poskytuje blokovacie rozhranie, ktoré umožňuje aplikáciám zablokovať akcie automatického uspania pomocou správcu napájania; ako príklad: správca balíkov operačného systému môže použiť toto rozhranie počas aktualizácie.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sr">Управник потрошње ИксФЦЕ-а има додатке сагласне са сучељима Д-сабирнице ради обавештавања других програма о тренутном ступњу напајања да би они смањили своју потрошњу, и омогућава сучеље које другим програмима омогућава да спрече радње самосталног успављивања преко управника потрошње; на пример,  управник пакета система би требао да користи ово сучеље при извршавању радњи надоградње.</p>
    <p xml:lang="th">นอกจากนี้ ระบบจัดการพลังงานของ Xfce ยังจัดเตรียมอินเทอร์เฟซ DBus ตามข้อกำหนดของ freedesktop เพื่อแจ้งอุปกรณ์ต่างๆ เกี่ยวกับระดับพลังงานปัจจุบัน เพื่อให้อุปกรณ์เหล่านั้นปรับการใช้พลังงานของตน และยังจัดเตรียมอินเทอร์เฟซสำหรับการระงับ ซึ่งทำให้โปรแกรมต่างๆ สามารถป้องกันการหลับอัตโนมัติผ่านระบบจัดการพลังงานได้ ตัวอย่างเช่น โปรแกรมจัดการแพกเกจของระบบปฏิบัติการควรใช้อินเทอร์เฟซดังกล่าวขณะดำเนินการอัปเดตระบบ</p>
    <p xml:lang="tr">Ek olarak,Xfce güç kaynağı geçerli güç düzeyi hakkında diğer uygulamaları bilgilendirmek için ücretsiz masaüstü uyumlu DBus arayüzleri dizisini sağlar,böylece onlar kendi güç tüketimini ayarlayabilirler,ve bu güç kaynağı üzerinden otomatik uyku eylemini engellemek amaçlı uygulamalar sağlar;örnek olarak,işletim sisteminin paket yöneticisi  güncelleme işlemleri gerçekleştirilirken bu arayüzü kullanması gerekir.</p>
    <p xml:lang="uk">На додаток, менеджер живлення Xfce впроваджує інтерфейси DBus, сумісні з правилами freedesktop, для інформування користувачів про поточний рівень заряду, завдяки чому користувачі можуть регулювати споживання енергії, а також інтерфейс гамування, який дозволяє користувачам  запобігати автоматичному засинанню через менеджер живлення; наприклад, менеджер пакунків операційної системи повинен використовувати цей інтерфейс поки іде оновлення.</p>
    <p xml:lang="zh_CN">与此同时，Xfce 电源管理器提供了一组符合 freedesktop.org 规范的 DBus 接口，用于通知其他应用程序以当前的电量级别，让它们调整电量使用，同时提供用于阻止电源管理器睡眠动作的接口；软件更新管理器应该使用此接口来保障更新操作顺利完成。</p>
    <p xml:lang="zh_TW">另外，Xfce 電源管理員提供了一組相容於 freedesktop 的 DBus 介面，以通知其他應用程式目前的電力狀態，這樣它們就可以調整電力消耗，它也提供了抑制介面，讓應用程式可以避免電源管理員自動進入睡眠；例如，作業系統的套件管理員需要在它執行升級動作時使用這個介面。</p>
    <p>Xfce power manager also provides a plugin for the Xfce and LXDE panels to control LCD brightness levels and to monitor battery and device charge levels.</p>
    <p xml:lang="bg">Xfce Power Manager също така включва и добавка за панелите на Xfce и LXDE, за контрол на яркостта на LCD екрана и наблюдение на нивата на заряд на батерията и зарядните устройства.</p>
    <p xml:lang="cs">Správce napájení pro Xfce také poskytuje zásuvný modul pro panely Xfce a LXDE pro ovládání úrovně jasu displejů LCD a pro sledování úrovní nabití baterie a zařízení.</p>
    <p xml:lang="de">Die Xfce-Energieverwaltung stellt ebenfalls ein Erweiterung für die Xfce- und die LXDE-Leiste zur Verfügung, um die Bildschirmhelligkeit zu steuern und um die Akkuladung und die Geräteladung zu überwachen.</p>
    <p xml:lang="en_AU">Xfce power manager also provides a plugin for the Xfce and LXDE panels to control LCD brightness levels and to monitor battery and device charge levels.</p>
    <p xml:lang="es">El administrador de energía de Xfce también provee un complemento para el panel de Xfce y LXDE para controlar los niveles de brillo de los LCD y monitorizar los niveles de carga y batería de los dispositivos.</p>
    <p xml:lang="fi">Xfce:n virranhallinta tarjoaa myös kaksi liitännäistä Xfce:n ja LXDE:n paneeleihin, yhden hallitsemaan näytön kirkkautta ja toisen laitteiden akkujen tilan seurantaan.</p>
    <p xml:lang="fr">Le gestionnaire d’alimentation Xfce fournit également un greffon pour les tableaux de bord Xfce et LXDE afin de contrôler le niveau de luminosité de l’écran LCD et de surveiller les niveaux de charge de la batterie et des périphériques.</p>
    <p xml:lang="he">מנהל צריכת חשמל Xfce מספק גם תוסף ללוחות של Xfce ושל LXDE כדי לשלוט ברמות הבהירות ולעקוב אחר הסוללה ורמות הטעינה של התקנים נוספים.</p>
    <p xml:lang="hr">Xfce upravitelj energijom također pruža dodatke za Xfce i LXDE koji omogućavaju upravljanje svjetlinom LCD zaslona te praćenje korištenja i napunjenosti baterije uređaja.</p>
    <p xml:lang="it">Il gestore di energia di Xfce fornisce anche un plugin per il pannello di Xfce e di LXDE che permette di controllare la luminosità dello schermo e monitorare i livelli di carica della batteria del dispositivo.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ja">また、Xfce パネル用と LXDE パネル用のプラグインも 2 種類提供しています。一つは LCD の輝度レベルを調整するもの、もう一つはバッテリやデバイスの充電レベルを監視するものです。</p>
    <p xml:lang="kk">Xfce эл. қорегін басқарушысы LCD экраны жарықтылығын басқару және батарея/құрылғылар заряд шамасын бақылау мүмкіндігін беретін Xfce және LXDE панельдері үшін плагинді ұсынады.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ko">Xfce 전원 관리자에서는 LCD 밝기를 조절하고 배터리와 장치 충전 상태를 감시하는 Xfce 및 LXDE용 플러그인도 제공합니다.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ms">Pengurus kuasa Xfce juga menyediakan satu pemalam panel Xfce dan LXDE untuk mengawal aras kecerahan LCD dan memantau aras pengecasan bateri dan peranti.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nb">Xfce strømbehandler tilbys også som et tillegg for Xfce og LXDE-paneler for å kontrollere LCD-lysstyrkenivå og oversikt over batteri og ladningsnivåer.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nl">Xfce-energiebeheerder levert ook een invoegtoepassing voor de werkbalken van Xfce en LXDE, om de helderheid van LCD-schermen in te stellen en om de ladingsniveaus te bewaken van accu's en apparaten.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt">O gestor de energia Xfce também fornece um plugin para o painel Xfce e LXDE para controlar o nível de brilho do LCD e mostar o nível de carga da bateria.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt_BR">O gerenciador de energia do Xfce também fornece um plug-in para os paineis do Xfce e LXDE para controlar os níveis de brilho do LCD e para monitorar os níveis de bateria e carga do dispositivo.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ro">Managerul de consum Xfce oferă un modul pentru panourile Xfce și LXDE pentru controlul luminozității LCD-urilor și pentru monitorizarea bateriei și a altor dispozitive ce necesită reîncărcare.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ru">Менеджер питания Xfce также предлагает модуль панелей Xfce и LXDE для регулировки яркости ЖК-дисплеев и контроля уровня заряда батарей и устройств.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sk">Správca napájania Xfce poskytuje aj zásuvný modul panela Xfce a LXDE na ovládanie úrovne jasu LCD a sledovanie úrovní batérie a nabíjacích zariadení.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sr">Управник потрошње Иксфце-а такође има прикључак за полице Иксфце-а и Ликсде-а за управљање ступњем осветљења и надзором батерије и пуњења.</p>
    <p xml:lang="th">ระบบจัดการพลังงานของ Xfce ยังได้จัดเตรียมปลั๊กอินสำหรับพาเนล Xfce และ LXDE สำหรับปรับความสว่างของจอ LCD และเฝ้าสังเกตระดับประจุไฟของแบตเตอรี่และอุปกรณ์ต่างๆ</p>
    <p xml:lang="tr">Ayrıca Xfce güç yöneticisi LCD parlaklığı seviyelerini,pil ve cihaz şarj seviyelerini izlemek için Xfce ve LXDE panelleri için eklenti sağlar.</p>
    <p xml:lang="uk">Менеджер живлення Xfce також пропонує додаток для панелей Xfce і LXDE для контролю рівня яскравості екрану і для контролю заряду акумулятора.</p>
    <p xml:lang="zh_CN">Xfce 电源管理器还提供了一个用于 Xfce 和 LXDE 面板的插件，用于管理 LCD 亮度以及其他设备的电量级别。</p>
    <p xml:lang="zh_TW">Xfce 電源管理員也為 Xfce 及 LXDE 面板提供了一個插件，用來控制液晶顯示器的亮度等級和監控電池及裝置的充電狀態。</p>
  </description>

  <screenshots>
    <screenshot type="default">
      <image width="624" height="351">http://git.xfce.org/xfce/xfce4-power-manager/plain/data/appdata/xfce4-power-manager-default.png</image>
    </screenshot>
  </screenshots>

  <url type="homepage">http://www.xfce.org/</url>
  <url type="bugtracker">https://bugzilla.xfce.org/</url>
  <url type="help">http://docs.xfce.org/xfce/xfce4-power-manager/start</url>

  <updatecontact>xfce4-dev@xfce.org</updatecontact>

  <project_group>XFCE</project_group>

  <provides>
    <binary>xfce4-power-manager</binary>
    <binary>xfce4-power-manager-settings</binary>
  </provides>

  <releases>
    <release version="1.3.2" timestamp="1408573857">
      <description>
        <p>This development release mostly fixes bugs and introduces better support for icon-themes by reducing the device icons and using standard names for them. It also features updated translations. The panel plugin has been renamed to Power Manager Plugin.</p>
        <p xml:lang="bg">Тази версия в процес на разработка фиксира грешки и е с подобрена поддръжка на темите за иконите при редуцирането на размера на иконите на устройствата и използването на техните стандартни имена. Актуализирана е езиковата поддръжка. Добавката за панела е преименувана на Добавка за Управление на захранването.</p>
        <p xml:lang="cs">Toto vývojové vydání především opravuje chyby a představuje zlepšenou podporu motivů ikon snížením počtu ikon zařízení a použitím standardních názvů. Také aktualizuje překlady. Zásuvný modul panelu se přejmenoval na Zásuvný modul Správce napájení.</p>
        <p xml:lang="de">Diese Entwicklungsversion behebt hauptsächlich Fehler und bringt bessere Unterstützung für Symbolthemen durch die Reduzierung der Gerätesymbole und unter Verwendung von Standardnamen für diese. Es verfügt auch über aktualisierte Übersetzungen. Die Leistenerweiterung wurde zu Energieverwaltungserweiterung umbenannt.</p>
        <p xml:lang="en_AU">This development release mostly fixes bugs and introduces better support for icon-themes by reducing the device icons and using standard names for them. It also features updated translations. The panel plugin has been renamed to Power Manager Plugin.</p>
        <p xml:lang="es">Esta versión de desarrollo corrige errores e introduce mejor soporte para temas de iconos mediante la reducción de los iconos de los dispositivos y el uso de nombres estándares para ellos. También cuenta con traducciones actualizadas. El nombre del complemento del panel se ha cambiado a «Complemento de administración de energía».</p>
        <p xml:lang="fr">Cette version de développement corrige principalement des bogues et permet une meilleure prise en charge des thèmes d’icônes en réduisant les icônes de périphérique et en leur attribuant des noms standards. Le greffon du tableau de bord a été renommé en « Greffon du gestionnaire d’alimentation ».</p>
        <p xml:lang="he">גרסת פיתוח זו בעיקר מתקנת תקלות ומציגה תמיכה טובה יותר בסמלים מותאמים אישית על ידי הפחתת סמלי ההתקנים ושימוש בשמות תקניים עבורים. גרסה זו גם מציעה עדכוני תרגומים. שם תוסף הלוח הוחלף לתוסף מנהל צריכת החשמל.</p>
        <p xml:lang="hr">Ova razvojna verzija ispravlja neke greške te nudi bolju podršku za različite teme ikona smanjajući veličinu ikona uređaja i koristeći standardna imena. Također donosi ažurirane prijevode. Dodatak za ploču je preimenovan u Dodatak Upravitelja energijom.</p>
        <p xml:lang="it">Questa versione di sviluppo principalmente sistema alcuni problemi e introduce un miglior supporto per i temi di icone riducendo il numero di icone dei dispositivi e utilizzando nomi standard. Sono stati inoltre aggiornate le traduzioni e il plugin del pannello è stato rinominato in Plugin del gestore di energia.</p>
        <p xml:lang="ja">この開発版リリースでは、ほとんどのバグが修正され、デバイスアイコンを減らして標準名を使用することによりアイコンテーマのサポートを改善しました。パネルプラグインは名称を「電源管理プラグイン」に変更し、翻訳を更新しました。</p>
        <p xml:lang="ko">개발 릴리즈는 대부분 버그를 수정하고 장치 아이콘을 줄이고 아이콘에 대한 표준 이름을 사용하여 아이콘 테마에 대한 개선 기능을 도입했습니다. 또한 번역도 업데이트했습니다. 패널 플러그인은 전원 관리자 플러그인으로 개명했습니다.</p>
        <p xml:lang="ms">Keluaran pembangunan ini kebanyakkannya pembaikan pepijat dan memperkenalkan sokongan lebih baik untuk tema ikon dengan mengurangkan ikon peranti dan menggunakan nama piawai untuk mereka. Ia juga fiturkan terjemahan dikemaskini. Pemalam panel telah dinamakan semula menjadi Pemalam Pengurus Kuasa.</p>
        <p xml:lang="nb">Denne utviklingsutgivelsen er for det meste myntet på feilretting og tilbyr bedre støtter for ikonbaserte drakter ved å redusere enhetsikoner og å bruke standardnavn på dem. Den inneholder også oppdaterte oversettelser. Paneltillegget har byttet navn til effektbehandlingstiillegg.</p>
        <p xml:lang="nl">Deze ontwikkelingseditie herstelt voornamelijk fouten en introduceert betere ondersteuning voor pictogramthema's, door het aantal apparaatpictogrammen te verminderen en er standaardnamen voor te gebruiken. Hij bevat ook bijgewerkte vertalingen. De werkbalk-invoegtoepassing is hernoemd naar Energiebeheerder-invoegtoepassing.</p>
        <p xml:lang="pt">Este lançamento corrige erros e introduz melhor suporte aos temas de ícones ao reduzir os ícones de dispositivo e usa nomes padrão para os mesmos. Também atualiza as traduções. O plugin do painel foi renomeado para Plugin Gestão de Energia.</p>
        <p xml:lang="pt_BR">Esta versão de desenvolvimento corrige principalmente erros e melhor suporte para temas de ícone, reduzindo os ícones de dispositivos e usando nomes padronizados. Também apresenta traduções atualizadas. O plug-in do painel foi renomeado para Plug-in Gerenciador de Energia.</p>
        <p xml:lang="ro">Această versiune de dezvoltare rezolvă unele probleme anterioare și aduce un suport mai bun pentru temele de iconițe, reducând mărimea iconițelor pentru dispozitive și folosind nume standard pentru ele. De asemenea, include traduceri actualizate. În plus, modulul pentru panou a fost redenumit.</p>
        <p xml:lang="ru">Этот разрабатываемый выпуск содержит в основном исправления ошибок и улучшенную поддержку тем значков путём использования для них стандартных имён. Также обновлены переводы. Модуль панели был переименован в «Модуль менеджера питания».</p>
        <p xml:lang="sk">Toto vývojové vydanie poväčšinou opravuje chyby a zavádza lepšiu podporu tém ikon znížením počtu ikon zariadení a použitím ich štandardných názvov. Obsahuje aj aktualizované preklady. Zásuvný modul panela bol premenovaný na Zásuvný modul správcu napájania.</p>
        <p xml:lang="sr">Ово развојно издање углавном исправља грешке и укључује бољу подршку за теме иконица смањивањем иконица уређаја и употребом њихових уобичајених имена. Преводи су освежени. Прикључак за полицу је преименован у Прикључак управника потрошњом.</p>
        <p xml:lang="th">รุ่นพัฒนารุ่นนี้โดยส่วนใหญ่เป็นการแก้บั๊กต่างๆ และได้ปรับปรุงการรองรับชุดไอคอนโดยลดไอคอนของอุปกรณ์ต่างๆ ลง และใช้ชื่อไอคอนมาตรฐาน นอกจากนี้ยังมีการปรับคำแปล และเปลี่ยนชื่อปลั๊กอินพาเนลเป็น "ปลั๊กอินจัดการพลังงาน"</p>
        <p xml:lang="tr">Bu geliştirme sürümü çoğunlukla hataları giderir ve onlar için standart isimler kullanarak ve cihaz simgelerini azaltarak simge temaları için daha iyi destek sunar.Ayrıca güncellenmiş çeviriler bulunmaktadır.Panel eklentisi Güç Yöneticisi Eklentisi olarak yeniden adlandırıldı.</p>
        <p xml:lang="uk">Цей розробницький випуск в основному містить виправлення і впроваджує кращу підтримку для тем іконок, зменшуючи іконки пристрою і використовуючи стандартні назви для них. Також має оновлені перекладів. Додаток панелі тепер названо Додаток менеджера живлення.</p>
        <p xml:lang="zh_CN">这个开发版本主要修复了一些问题并改进（标准化）了图标主题支持。当然，软件翻译也更新了（成就感 UP）。此面板插件已更名为“电源管理器插件”。</p>
        <p xml:lang="zh_TW">這個開發版本主要在修復臭蟲及以減少裝置圖示來對圖示主題獲得更佳的支援，那些被移除的裝置圖示將會使用標準的名稱。它也提供了更新的翻譯。此面板插件被重新命名為電力管理員插件。</p>
      </description>
    </release>

    <release version="1.3.1" timestamp="1407741245">
      <description>
        <p>This development release fixes bugs with suspend and hibernate. It also improves the panel-plugin, incorporating the functionality of the (now dropped) brightness panel-plugin. A new popup notification was added to account for keyboard brightness changes and the Power Manager now also controls the X11 blank times.</p>
        <p xml:lang="bg">Тази версия в процес на разработка фиксира бъгове, свързани с приспиването и хибернацията. Също така, подобрения на добавката за панела, включващи функционалността (сега е намалена) на добавката за управление на яркостта. Ново изскачащо уведомление е добавено за отчитане яркостта при промяна с клавишна комбинация и управителят Мощност сега също контролира периодите на неактивност на X11.</p>
        <p xml:lang="cs">Toto vývojové vydání opravuje chyby související s režimem spánku a hibernací.  Také vylepšuje zásuvný modul pro panel, včetně funkcionality (nyní vynechaného) zásuvného modulu panelu pro nastavení jasu. Byla přidána nová notifikace pro změny jasu klávesnice a Správce napájení nyní také ovládá prodlevu před vypnutím displeje pomocí interních rutin prostředí X11.</p>
        <p xml:lang="de">Diese Entwicklungsversion behebt Fehler mit Bereitschaft und Ruhezustand. Es verbessert auch die Leistenerweiterung, unter Einbeziehung der Funktionalität der (jetzt fallengelassen) Helligkeitsleistenerweiterung. Eine neue Benachrichtigungsfunktion wurde hinzugefügt, um über Helligkeitsänderungen per Tastatur zu berichten und die Energieverwaltung steuert jetzt auch die X11 Leerlaufzeiten.</p>
        <p xml:lang="en_AU">This development release fixes bugs with suspend and hibernate. It also improves the panel-plugin, incorporating the functionality of the (now dropped) brightness panel-plugin. A new popup notification was added to account for keyboard brightness changes and the Power Manager now also controls the X11 blank times.</p>
        <p xml:lang="es">Esta versión de desarrollo corrige errores con suspensión e hibernación. También mejora el complemento del panel que incorpora la funcionalidad del (ahora abandonado) Complemento de brillo del panel. Una nueva notificación emergente se añadió para dar cuenta de los cambios de brillo del teclado y el Administrador de energía ahora también controla los tiempos de pantalla en blanco de X11.</p>
        <p xml:lang="fr">Cette version de développement corrige des bogues relatifs à la mise en veille et la mise en veille prolongée. Elle améliore également le greffon du tableau de bord, en incorporant les fonctionnalités du greffon de luminosité (maintenant obsolète). Une nouvelle notification contextuelle a été ajoutée pour rendre compte des changements de luminosité du clavier et le gestionnaire d’alimentation contrôle désormais les écrans vides X11.</p>
        <p xml:lang="he">גרסת פיתוח זו מתקנת תקלות בפעולות ההשהיה והתרדמת. היא גם משפרת את תוספי הלוח, תוך שילוב תכונות של תוסף לוח הבהירות (שפיתוחו נזנח). התרעות קופצות חדשות נוספו לחשבון לשינויי בהירות המקלדת ומעתה מנהל צריכת החשמל שולט גם בזמני ההחשכה של X11.</p>
        <p xml:lang="hr">Ova razvojna verzija ispravlja greške sa suspenzijom i hibernacijom sustava. Donosi poboljšanja u dodatak za ploču pripajanjem funkcionalnosti dodatka za svjetlinu zaslona. Dodana je skočna (popup) obavijest za promijene u svijetlini tipkovnice te je dodana kontrola za X11 blank times.</p>
        <p xml:lang="it">Questa versione di sviluppo sistema alcuni problemi relativi alla sospensione e all'ibernazione. Viene anche migliorato il plugin del pannello incorporando le funzionalità del (ora abbandonato) plugin per il controllo della luminosità. È stata aggiunta una nuova notifica a comparsa per il cambio di luminosità della tastiera e il gestore di energia ora controlla anche i blank time di X11.</p>
        <p xml:lang="ja">この開発版リリースでは、サスペンドおよびハイバネートに関するバグが修正されました。他に、パネルプラグインを改善し、輝度プラグインと機能統合されました (輝度プラグインは廃止)。新しくキーボードの輝度が変更されたときの通知機能が追加され、電源管理で X11 ブランク時間を制御できるようになりました。</p>
        <p xml:lang="ko">이 개발 릴리즈는 대기 및 최대 절전 기능으 버그를 수정했습니다. 패널 플러그인을 개선했으며, (이제는 버린) 밝기 조절 패널 플러그인의 기능을 통합했습니다. 새 풍선 도움말 알림을 추가하여 키보드 밝기 변화를 잡았으며, 전원 관리자는 이제 X11 화면 공백처리에 필요한 시간을 조절할 수 있습니다.</p>
        <p xml:lang="ms">Keluaran pembangunan ini membaiki pepijat dengan tangguh dan hibernasi. Ia juga menambahbaik pemalam-panel, yang menggabungkan kefungsian pemalam-panel kecerahan (kini dibatalkan). Satu pemberitahuan timbul baharu telah ditambah pada akaun untuk perubahan kecerahan papan kekunci dan Pengurus Kuasa kini dapat mengawal skrin kosong X11.</p>
        <p xml:lang="nb">Denne utviklingsutgivelsen ordner opp i feil tilknyttet hvile og dvalemodus, den forbedrer også paneltillegget, ved å legge til funksjonalitet i (det nå forkastede) lysstyringspaneltillegget. En ny oppsprettsvarsling ble lagt til for å ta høyde for tastaturlysstyrkeendringer og effektbehandlerern styrer nå også utblankingstider for X11.</p>
        <p xml:lang="nl">Deze ontwikkelingseditie herstelt fouten met pauzestand en slaapstand. Hij verbetert tevens de werkbalk-invoegtoepassing, door er de functionaliteit aan toe te voegen van de (nu geschrapte) werkbalk-invoegtoepassing voor helderheid. Er is een nieuwe opduikmelding toegevoegd voor helderheidveranderingen van het toetsenbord en de Energiebeheerder beheerst nu ook de tijdstippen voor 'op zwart gaan' van X11.</p>
        <p xml:lang="pt">Este lançamento corrige erros da suspensão e hibernação. Também melhora o plugin do painel, incorporando a funcionalidade do (agora arrastável) plugin de brilho. Uma nova janela de notificação foi adicionada para o brilho do teclado e o gestor de energia também controla o desligamento do X11.</p>
        <p xml:lang="pt_BR">Esta versão de desenvolvimento corrige erros relacionados a suspensão e hibernação. Também melhora o plug-in do painel, incorporando a funcionalidade do (agora extinto) plug-in do painel de brilho. Uma nova notificação pop-up foi adicionada para apresentar as mudanças do brilho do teclado e o Gerenciador de Energia agora controla os tempos do monitor em branco do X11.</p>
        <p xml:lang="ro">Această versiune de dezvoltare rezolvă unele probleme cu suspendarea și hibernarea. De asemenea, îmbunătățește modulul pentru panou, încorporând funcționalitatea vechiului modul de panou pentru controlul luminozității. Un nou stil de notificări a fost creat pentru schimbările de luminozitate a tastaturii, iar managerul de consum controlează acum și opțiunile X11 de protecție a ecranului.</p>
        <p xml:lang="ru">Этот разрабатываемый выпуск содержит исправления ошибок ждущего и спящего режимов. Также улучшены модули панели, включая функциональность (теперь заброшенного) модуля яркости. Новое всплывающее уведомление было добавлено для изменения яркости с клавиатуры и «Менеджер питания» теперь управляет временем гашением экрана X11.</p>
        <p xml:lang="sk">Toto vývojové vydanie opravuje chyby s uspaním a hibernáciou. Tiež vylepšuje zásuvný modul panela zabudovaním funkcií (teraz už nepoužívaného) zásuvného modulu jasu. Boli pridané nové upozornenia na sledovanie zmien jasu klávesnicou a Správca napájania teraz riadi aj časy X11 blank.</p>
        <p xml:lang="sr">Ово развојно издање исправља грешке код обуставе и замрзавања. Такође, побољшан је прикључак полице са уграђеним могућностима прикључка полице за осветљење чији је развој обустављен. Додато је ново искачуће обавештење за измену осветљења тастатуром, а управник напајања сада управља временом затамњивања икс11.</p>
        <p xml:lang="th">รุ่นพัฒนารุ่นนี้มีการแก้บั๊กเกี่ยวกับการพักเครื่องและจำศีลเครื่อง และยังมีการปรับปรุงปลั๊กอินพาเนล โดยรวมเอาความสามารถของปลั๊กอินปรับความสว่าง (ซึ่งขณะนี้ถูกตัดออกแล้ว) เข้ามา มีการเพิ่มการแจ้งเหตุแบบผุดขึ้นเพื่อแสดงการปรับความสว่างผ่านแป้นพิมพ์ และขณะนี้ระบบจัดการพลังงานยังควบคุมเวลาดับจอของ X11 อีกด้วย</p>
        <p xml:lang="tr">Bu geliştirme sürümü suspend ve hibernate ile hataları giderir. Aynı zamanda (now dropped) parlaklık panel eklentisi işlevselliğini birleştiren,panel eklentisi geliştirir.Yeni açılan bildirim klavye parlaklık değişiklikleri  için hesaba eklendi ve ayrıca şimdi Güç Yöneticisi X11  boş zamanlarda kontrol ediliyor.</p>
        <p xml:lang="uk">Цей розробницький випуск містить виправлення проблем з засинанням і сплячкою. Також покращено додаток панелі, включаючи функціональність (зараз покинутого) додатку регуляції яскравості. Нові вигулькні повідомлення додано для зміни яскравості клавіатурою, тепер Менеджер живлення контролює паузи X11.</p>
        <p xml:lang="zh_CN">此开发版本修复了待机和休眠动作的一些问题。同时改进了面板插件，并包含了（已被弃用的）亮度控制插件。添加了键盘背光亮度的弹出通知，电源管理器现在还控制着 X11 清屏时间。</p>
        <p xml:lang="zh_TW">此開發版本修復了暫停及休眠。它也改善了面板插件，並結合了(現在已放棄的)面板插件。加入新的彈出通知來說明鍵盤的亮度變更，而電力管理員現在也可以控制X11的空白時間。</p>
      </description>
    </release>

    <release version="1.3.0" timestamp="1401646266">
      <description>
        <p>This development release introduces a lot of new features, among them suspending/hibernation without systemd and UPower>=0.99. It allows for individual control of systemd-inhibition, a new panel plugin to monitor battery and device charge levels replaces the trayicon. The settings dialog has been completely restructured for better oversight and many open bugs have been fixed and translations have been updated.</p>
        <p xml:lang="bg">Това издание въвежда много нови функции, сред които временно преустановяване / хибернация без systemd и UPower> = 0.99. Тя дава възможност за индивидуален контрол на systemd-инхибиране, нова добавка за панела за следене на батерията и зарядно устройство, който замества иконата в зоната за уведомяване. Диалоговия прозорец за настройките е напълно преструктуриран за по-добър контрол, много открити бъгове са фиксирани, а преводите са актуализирани.</p>
        <p xml:lang="cs">Tato vývojová verze představuje mnoho nových funkcí a vlastností, mezi nimiž jsou režim spánku a hibernace bez služeb systemd a UPower ve verzi 0.99 a vyšší. Umožňuje individuální ovládání potlačení služby systemd, nový zásuvný modul pro panel pro sledování úrovně nabíjení baterie a zařízení nahrazuje ikonu v systémové oblasti. Struktura dialogového okna nastavení byla kompletně změněna pro lepší přehlednost, bylo opraveno mnoho otevřených bugů a byly aktualizovány překlady.</p>
        <p xml:lang="de">Diese Entwicklungsversion bringt eine Menge neuer Funktionen, darunter das Versetzen in den Bereitschaftsmodus/Ruhezustand ohne systemd und UPower>=0.99. Sie erlaubt die individuelle Steuerung von systemd-inhibition, eine neue Erweiterung für die Leiste, zur Überwachung des Ladezustandes von Akkus und Geräten, ersetzt das Symbol in der Benachrichtigungsfläche. Der Einstellungsdialog wurde zwecks besserer Übersicht komplett restrukturiert, viele offene Fehler wurden bereinigt und Übersetzungen überarbeitet.</p>
        <p xml:lang="en_AU">This development release introduces a lot of new features, among them suspending/hibernation without systemd and UPower>=0.99. It allows for individual control of systemd-inhibition, a new panel plugin to monitor battery and device charge levels replaces the trayicon. The settings dialog has been completely restructured for better oversight and many open bugs have been fixed and translations have been updated.</p>
        <p xml:lang="es">Esta versión de desarrollo introduce un montón de nuevas características, entre ellas la suspensión/hibernación sin «systemd» y «UPower» >= 0.99. Permite el control individual de  «systemd-inhibition», un nuevo complemento del panel para monitorizar la batería y los niveles de carga del dispositivo el cual sustituye al icono de la bandeja de notificación. El diálogo de configuración ha sido completamente restructurado para una mejor supervisión y muchos errores han sido corregidos y las traducciones han sido actualizadas.</p>
        <p xml:lang="fr">Cette version de développement introduit beaucoup de nouvelles fonctionnalités, parmi lesquelles la mise en veille prolongée sans systemd et UPower>=0.99. Un contrôle individuel de systemd-inhibition est possible, un nouveau greffon du tableau de bord pour surveiller les niveaux de charge de la batterie et des périphériques remplace l’icône de la zone de notification. La fenêtre des paramètres a été complètement restructurée pour une meilleure vue d’ensemble, beaucoup de bogues ouverts ont été corrigés et les traductions ont été mises à jour.</p>
        <p xml:lang="he">גרסת פיתוח זו מציגה שלל תכונות חדשות, ביניהן השהיה/תרדמת ללא systemd ו־UPower>=0.99. גרסה זו מאפשרת שליטה יחידנית במניעת המערכת, תוסף לוח חדש למעקב אחר הסוללה ורמות טעינה של התקנים נוספים מחליף את סמל המערכת. דו־שיח ההגדרות נבנה מחדש לחלוטין לסקירה טובה יותר ותקלות פתוחות רבות תוקנו לרבות עדכוני תרגומים.</p>
        <p xml:lang="hr">Ova razvojna verzija uvodi mnogo novih značajki, među njima mogućnost pripravnosti/hibernacije bez systemd aplikacije i UPower>=0.99. Pruža individualnu kontrolu za systemd-inhibition, novi dodatak za ploču koji nadzire bateriju i razinu napunjenosti uređaja zamjenjuje ikonu u sistemskom pladnju. Prozor s postavkama je u potpunosti restrukturiran radi boljeg pregleda,  ispravljene su mnoge greške te su ažurirani prijevodi.</p>
        <p xml:lang="it">Questo rilascio di sviluppo introduce molte nuove caratteristiche tra cui la sospensione/ibernazione senza systemd e UPower>=0.99, la possibilità di controllare individualmente l'inibizione di systemd, un nuovo plugin del pannello per controllare la batteria e il livello di carica del dispositivo in luogo dell'icona nel vassoio di sistema. La finestra delle impostazioni è stata completamente ristrutturata, sono stati corretti diversi problemi e le traduzioni sono state aggiornate.</p>
        <p xml:lang="ja">この開発版リリースでは多くの新機能を導入しました。systemd および UPower>=0.99 なしでのサスペンド/ハイバネートでは systemd-inhibit の個別制御が行え、トレイアイコンはバッテリインジケータープラグインに置き換えられました。設定ダイアログは完全に書き直され、多くのバグが修正されました。</p>
        <p xml:lang="ko">이 개발 릴리스에서는 여러가지 새 기능을 도입했는데 systemd와 UPower>=0.99를 뺀 절전/최대 절전 기능이 여기에 포함되어 있습니다. systemd-inhibition의 개별 제어가 가능하며, 배터리와 장치 충전 상태를 표시줄 아이콘으로 나타내는 새 패널 플러그인을 제공합니다. 설정 대화상자는 더 나은 모습을 보여드리기 위해 재구성했으며, 수많은 버그를 수정하고, 번역을 새로 올렸습니다.</p>
        <p xml:lang="ms">Keluaran pembangunan ini memperkenalkan banyak fitur baharu, diantaranya menangguh/hibernasi tanpa systemd dan UPower>=0.99. Ia membolehkan kawalan systemd-inhibition secara individu, satu pemalam panel baharu untu memantau bateri dan aras pengecasan peranti yang menggantikan ikon talam. Dialog tetapan telah distruktur sepenuhnya untuk pandangan lebih baik dan banyak pepijat telah dibaiki dan juga terjemahan telah dikemaskini.</p>
        <p xml:lang="nb">Denne utviklingsversjonen har mange nye trekkplaster, blandt dem hvile/dvalemodus uten systemd og UPower>=0.99. Individuell kontroll av systemd-inngripen, et nytt programtillegg for panelet for batterioversikt med ladningsnivå, som erstatter ikonet i systemkurven. Innstillingspanelet har blitt ombygd for bedre oversikt, oversettelser har blitt oppdatert og mange feil har blitt rettet.</p>
        <p xml:lang="nl">Deze ontwikkelversie introduceert vele nieuwe functies, waaronder pauzestand/slaapstand zonder systemd en UPower>=0.99. Hij biedt de mogelijkheid voor individueel beheersen van systemd-inhibition. Een nieuwe werkbalkinvoegtoepassing om de ladingsniveaus van accu en apparaat te bewaken vervangt het systeemvakpictogram. De instellingendialoog is volledig geherstructureerd voor beter overzicht, vele openstaande fouten zijn hersteld en vertalingen zijn bijgewerkt.</p>
        <p xml:lang="pt">Esta versão em desenvolvimento introduz muitos novos recursos, entre os quais suspensão/hibernação sem o systemd e UPower>=0.99. Este permite para controlo individual do systemd-inhibition, Um novo plugin de painel para monitorar os niveis de energia da bateria e dos dispositivos, substitui o trayicon. A caixa de diálogo Configurações foi completamente reestruturada para melhor supervisão e muitos erros em aberto foram corrigidos e traduções foram atualizadas.</p>
        <p xml:lang="pt_BR">Esta versão de desenvolvimento introduz uma série de novas funcionalidades, entre elas a suspensão/hibernação sem systemd e UPower>=0.99. Permite o controle individual do systemd-inhibition, um novo plug-in do painel para monitorar a bateria e os níveis de carga do dispositivo o qual substitui o ícone da bandeija. O diálogo de configurações foi completamente reestruturado para melhor supervisão, muitos erros foram corrigidos e as traduções foram atualizadas.</p>
        <p xml:lang="ro">Această versiune de dezvoltare introduce o mulțime de noi facilități, printre ele suspendarea și hibernarea fără systemd cu o versiune UPower mai mare de 0.99. Permite control granular pentru systemd-inhibition, iar vechea iconiță din zona de notificare a fost înlocuită cu un modul nou de panou pentru monitorizarea bateriei și încărcarea dispozitivelor. Fereastra cu opțiuni a fost complet restructurată pentru o utilizare mai facilă, multe probleme raportate au fost rezolvate, iar traducerile actualizate.</p>
        <p xml:lang="ru">В разрабатываемом выпуске представлено много новых особенностей, среди них ждущий/спящий режим без systemd и UPower ≥ 0.99. Возможно индивидуальное управление systemd-inhibition. Новый модуль панели для отслеживания заряда батареи заменил значок в системном лотке. Диалог настроек был полностью реорганизован для улучшения обзора. Исправлены многие сообщённые ошибки и обновлены переводы.</p>
        <p xml:lang="sk">Toto vývojové vydanie zavádza veľa nových vlastností, spolu s uspávaním/hibernáciou bez systemd a UPower>=0.99. Umožňuje individuálne riadenie systemd-inhibition, nový zásuvný modul panela na sledovanie úrovne nabíjanie batérie a zariadenia nahradzuje ikonu oznamovacej oblasti. Dialóg nastavení bol kompletne zmenený kvôli zlepšeniu prehľadnosti a bolo opravených veľa nahlásených chýb a aktualizovaných veľa prekladov.</p>
        <p xml:lang="sr">Ово развојно издање представља нове могућности, међу њима и обуставу/замрзавање без програма systemd и UPower>=0.99. Омогућава појединачно управљање мировањем система, нови прикључак полице за надгледање батерије и ступња пуњења уређаја замењује иконицу обавештајне области. Прозорчету поставки је потпуно измењен распоред ради бољег прегледа, многе грешке су исправљене, а преводи су освежени.</p>
        <p xml:lang="th">รุ่นพัฒนารุ่นนี้มีการเพิ่มความสามารถใหม่เข้ามามากมาย เช่น การพักเครื่อง/จำศีลเครื่องโดยใช้ systemd และ UPower>=0.99, สามารถควบคุมการระงับผ่าน systemd เป็นรายตัวได้, มีปลั๊กอินใหม่สำหรับพาเนลสำหรับเฝ้าสังเกตระดับประจุไฟแบตเตอรี่และอุปกรณ์ต่างๆ ซึ่งมาแทนที่ไอคอนถาด, กล่องโต้ตอบตั้งค่ามีการปรับโครงสร้างใหม่หมดเพื่อให้เห็นภาพรวมได้ดียิ่งขึ้น, และมีการแก้บั๊กหลายรายการ รวมทั้งการปรับคำแปลต่างๆ</p>
        <p xml:lang="tr">Bu geliştirme sürümü   aralarında systemd ve Upower>=0.99 olmadan suspending/hibernation olduğu gibi bir çok yeni özellik tanıttı,.Bu surüm systemd-inhibition kontrolünü sağlar,pili izlemek için yeni panel eklentisini verir ve trayicon cihazının jarj  seviyelerini değiştirir.İletişim ayarları daha iyi gözetim için tamamen yeniden yapılandırıldı ve bir çok açık hatalar düzeltildi ve çeviriler güncellendi.</p>
        <p xml:lang="uk">Цей розробницький випуск містить багато нових можливостей, серед них засинання/сплячка без systemd і UPower>=0.99. Це дозволяє індивідуальний контроль над гамуванням systemd, новий додаток для моніторингу акумулятора і рівнів системного заряду заміняє іконку панелі. Діалог налаштування повністю переписано для кращого сприйняття, багато відкритих проблем вирішено і оновлено переклади.</p>
        <p xml:lang="zh_CN">此开发版本带来了许多新特性，其中包括不需要 systemd 即可休眠和待机，以及 UPower >= 0.99。此版本允许单一控制 systemd-inhibition，以及一个用于监控设备电量的插件。设置对话框也被完全重新设计以提供更好的体验，许多问题也被修复了。当然，翻译也被更新。</p>
        <p xml:lang="zh_TW">這個開發版本採用了許多新的功能，其中包括了不需要 systemd 及 UPower>=0.99 的暫停及休眠。它可以不使用 systemd 的抑制功能而獨立控制，新的面板插件以監視電池及裝置的充電狀態並取代通知區域圖示。設定對話框也完全重建，以更佳的監督，並有許多開放的臭蟲也已經被修復，翻譯也更新了。</p>
      </description>
    </release>
  
    <release version="1.2.0" timestamp="1335645654">
      <description>
        <p>This stable release fixes compilation problems, a memory leak and a few other minor bugs. Furthermore it provides updated translations.</p>
        <p xml:lang="bg">Тази стабилна версия поправя компилационни проблеми, загуба на памет и няколко други малки бъгове. Освен това се предлагат актуализирани преводи.</p>
        <p xml:lang="cs">Tato stabilní verze souhrnně opravuje potíže, úniky paměti a několik menších chyb. Dále také aktualizuje překlady.</p>
        <p xml:lang="de">Diese stabile Version korrigiert Kompilierungsprobleme, ein Speicherleck und einige kleinere Fehler. Überdies wurden die Übersetzungen überarbeitet.</p>
        <p xml:lang="en_AU">This stable release fixes compilation problems, a memory leak and a few other minor bugs. Furthermore it provides updated translations.</p>
        <p xml:lang="es">Esta versión estable corrige problemas de compilación, una pérdida de memoria y algunos errores menores. Además, ofrece traducciones actualizadas.</p>
        <p xml:lang="fr">Cette version stable corrige des problèmes de compilation, une fuite de mémoire et quelques autres bogues mineurs. En outre, elle apporte des mises à jour des traductions.</p>
        <p xml:lang="he">גרסה יציבה זו מתקנת בעיות הידור, זליגת זיכרון ומספר תקלות קטנות נוספות. יתרה מכך, עדכונים של מספר תרגומים.</p>
        <p xml:lang="hr">Ova stabilna verzija riješava probleme s kompilacijm, osipanje memorije i nekoliko drugih sitni problema. Uz to pruža ažurane prijevode.</p>
        <p xml:lang="hu">Ez a stabil kiadás fordítási problémákat, egy memóriaszivárgást és néhány egyéb kisebb hibát javít. Továbbá frissített fordításokat biztosít.</p>
        <p xml:lang="it">Questo rilascio stabile sistema alcuni problemi di compilazione, un eccessivo consumo di memoria e alcuni altri bug minori. Fornisce inoltre traduzioni aggiornate.</p>
        <p xml:lang="ja">この安定版リリースではコンパイルの問題、メモリリーク、およびいくつかの小さなバグが修正されました。</p>
        <p xml:lang="kk">Бұл тұрақты шығарылым компиляция мәселелерін, жадыны жоғалту және басқа ақаулықтарды түзейді. Сонымен қатар, жаңартылған аудармаларды ұсынады.</p>
        <p xml:lang="ko">이 안정 릴리스에서는, 메모리 누수와 기타 자잘한 버그 등의 복잡한 문제를 수정했습니다. 게다가 새로 올린 번역도 있습니다.</p>
        <p xml:lang="ms">Keluaran stabil ini membaiki masalah kompilasi, kebocoran ingatan dan beberapa pepijat kecil yang lain. Selain itu ia menyediakan terjemahan yang telah dikemaskini.</p>
        <p xml:lang="nb">Denne stabile utgaven fikser kompileringsproblemer, en minnelekkasje og flere andre småfeil. Også nye oversettelser har kommet med.</p>
        <p xml:lang="nl">Deze stabiele versie herstelt compilatieproblemen, een geheugenlek en een paar kleinere fouten. Buitendien levert hij bijgewerkte vertalingen.</p>
        <p xml:lang="pl">Wydanie to naprawia problemy z kompilacją, wycieki pamięci oraz kilka innych drobnych błędów. Dodatkowo zaktualizowano tłumaczenia.</p>
        <p xml:lang="pt">Esta versão estável resolve problemas de compilação, uma perda de memória e outros erros menores. Além disso, fornece traduções atualizadas.</p>
        <p xml:lang="pt_BR">Esta versão estável corrige problemas de compilação, um vazamento de memória e alguns outros pequenos bugs. Além disso, fornece traduções atualizadas.</p>
        <p xml:lang="ro">Această versiune stabilă repară unele erori de compilare, o problemă cu consumul de memorie și alte probleme mai mărunte. În plus, include traduceri actualizate.</p>
        <p xml:lang="ru">В данном стабильном выпуске исправлены проблемы сборки, утечки памяти и некоторые другие ошибки, а также обновлены переводы.</p>
        <p xml:lang="sk">Toto stabilné vydanie opravuje problémy kompilácie, únik pamäte a niekoľko ďalších menších chýb. Okrem toho prináša aktualizované preklady.</p>
        <p xml:lang="sr">У стабилном издању су решене потешкоће са компиловањем, цурењем меморије и другим малим бубама. Преводи су надограђени.</p>
        <p xml:lang="th">รุ่นเสถียรรุ่นนี้มีการแก้ปัญหาการคอมไพล์ อุดหน่วยความจำรั่วไหล และแก้บั๊กเล็กน้อยอื่นๆ นอกจากนี้ ยังมีการปรับคำแปลต่างๆ ด้วย</p>
        <p xml:lang="tr">Bu kararlı sürüm derleme sorunları,bellek sızıntısı ve diğer küçük hataları giderir.Ayrıca güncelleştirilmiş çevirileri sağlar.</p>
        <p xml:lang="uk">Цей стабільний випуск містить виправлення проблем з компіляцією, витоками пам’яті і кілька інших проблем. Також має оновлені переклади. </p>
        <p xml:lang="zh_CN">当前的发行版本修复了编译问题，内存泄漏已经其它小bug。另外还更新了翻译内容。</p>
        <p xml:lang="zh_TW">這個穩定版本修復了相容性的問題，記憶體洩漏及與其他一些次要的臭蟲。此外，它也更新了翻譯。</p>
      </description>
    </release>
  </releases>

</component>